Fellow warriors. this is Sheldor the Conqueror.
Amis guerriers, ici Sheldor le Conquérant.
We are about to enter Atzel's fortress.
Nous allons bientôt entrer.
Now. this is a long run. so let's do another bladder check.
Ça va être long alors vérifions nos vessies.
All right. Barry. we'll wait for you again. but you really should see a doctor.
O.K, Barry, on t‘attend encore mais tu devrais voir un médecin.
Sheldor is AFK.
Sheldor est ABS.
Penny. are you experiencing some sort of difficulty?
Penny, rencontres-tu une difficulté ?
Yes. I can't get my stupid door open.
Je n'arrive pas a ouvrir la porte.
You appear to have put your car key in the door lock. Are you aware of that?
Tu as mis ta clé de voiture dans la serrure. En as-tu conscience ?
Yeah.
Oui.
All right. then.
Très bien.
PENNY: Damn it. damn it. damn it.
Zut, zut et zut.
Would it be possible for you to do this a little more quietly?
Pourrais-tu faire ca un peu moins fort ?
-I can't get the damn key out. -That's not surprising.
- Cette fichue clé ne sort pas. - C‘est normal.
That Baldwin lock on your door uses traditional edge-mounted cylinders...
Cette serrure Baldwin exige une clé traditionnelle
...whereas the key for your Volkswagen uses a center-cylinder system.
tandis que la clé de ta Volkswagen n‘est pas conçue de la sorte.
Thank you. Sheldon.
Merci, Sheldon.
You're welcome.
De rien.
Point of inquiry: Why did you put your car key in the door lock?
Question : pourquoi as-tu inséré ta clé de voiture ?
I'll tell you why. Today I had an audition.
Aujourd'hui, j'ai eu une audition.
It took me two hours to get there. I waited an hour for my turn.
Deux heures de trajet. Une heure d'attente.
Before I could start. they told me I look too Midwest for the part.
On m‘a dit que je faisais trop “Midwest.“
Too Midwest. What the hell does that even mean?
Trop “Midwest.“ Ça veut dire quoi ?
The American Midwest was mostly settled by Scandinavian and Germanic peoples...
Cette région était peuplée essentiellement de scandinaves et d'allemands
-...who have characteristic facial-- -I know what it means.
- qui ont des traits typiques... - Je sais.
God. l have been in LA. for almost two years now.
Je suis à LA. depuis près de deux ans.
I haven't gotten a single acting job. I've accomplished nothing.
Je n'ai pas eu un seul rôle. Je n'ai rien accompli.
Haven't gotten a raise at work. Haven't even had sex in six months.
Ni fais l‘amour depuis six mois.
And when l was walking up those stairs a fly flew in my mouth and I ate it.
Et en montant les marches, j'ai avalé une mouche.
Well. actually. insects are a dietary staple in many cultures.
Beaucoup de peuples mangent des insectes.
They're almost pure protein.
Des protéines pures.
Oh. son of a bitch.
Oh, bon sang.
The condensation on your frozen foods...
La condensation sur tes produits
...weakened the structural integrity of the bag.
congelés a réduit la résistance du sac.
But returning to your key conundrum. you should call a locksmith.
Pour en revenir a ta clé, appelle un serrurier.
-Have him open the door for you. -I did.
- Il t'ouvrira. - C‘est fait.
He said he'll get here when he gets here.
Il arrivera quand il arrivera.
You're frustrated because he phrased his reply in a meaningless tautology?
Tu es frustrée car il a répondu par un pléonasme.
No. I am frustrated because I am a failure at everything...
Non. Je suis frustrée car je suis un échec total
...and my breath smells like fly.
et que j'ai une haleine de mouche.
There. there.
La. la.
Would you prefer to wait in our apartment?
Veux-tu attendre chez nous ?
No, I'd rather sit on this freezing floor. sobbing like a 3-year-old.
Non, je préfére pleurnicher sur le sol gelé.
All right. then.
D‘accord.
For God's sake.
Bon sang.
Just when I think I've gotten the hang of sarcasm.
Juste quand je croyais avoir pigé Ie sarcasme.
Make yourself comfortable.
Mets—toi a l‘aise.
Not there.
Pas la.
Sheldor is back online.
Sheldor est de retour.
Sheldor?
Sheldor ?
The Conqueror.
Le Conquérant.
What are you doing?
Que fais-tu ?
AFK.
ABS.
I'm playing “Age of Conan." an online multiplayer game...
Je joue a “Age of Conan." un jeu en ligne
...set in the universe of Robert E. Howard's Conan the Barbarian.
qui se déroule dans l‘univers de Conan le Barbare.
Sheldor back online.
Sheldor est de retour.
-What's AFK? -AFK.
- C‘est quoi, ABS ? - ABS.
Away from keyboard.
Absent.
Oh. I see.
Je vois.
What does that stand for?
Ça veut dire quoi ?
Yes. but what does it stand for?
Oui, mais qu'est-ce que ca veut dire ?
And just click on the enchanted boots to put them on.
Clique sur les bottes enchantées pour les mettre.
I don't know. Can I see them in another color?
J‘hésite. Je peux les voir dans une autre couleur ?
Just click on them.
Clique dessus.
Now. congratulations. you are now a level-three warrior.
Félicitations, tu es un guerrier de niveau trois.
-What's going on? -Guess what? I'm a level-three warrior.
- Qu'y a-t-il ? - Je suis un guerrier niveau 3.
Do you know there are groceries outside of your apartment?
Sais-tu qu'il y a des courses devant chez toi ?
Yeah. yeah. yeah. Shh.
Oui, oui.
| only bring it up because your ice cream's melting and it's starting to attract wildlife.
Je tele dis car ta glace fond et attire la faune.
Uh-huh. Do | stay in the jungle or go towards the beach?
La jungle oula plage ?
Doesn't matter. you're looking for treasure.
- Peu importe, tu cherches le trésor. - O.K.
-Wait. where are you going? -Go ahead. You're okay.
- Attends, où vas-tu ? - Vas-y. Ça va.
If you run into crocodiles. just kick them with your boots.
Si tu vois des crocodiles, frappe—les avec tes hottes.
Wanna catch me up?
Tu m'expliques ?
Well. uh. let's see. She attempted to open her apartment with her car key...
Elle a essayé d'ouvrir sa porte avec la clé de sa voiture
...because her face is overly Midwestern. Uh....
car elle ressemble a une fille du Midwest.
She hasn't had sex in six months.
Pas de sexe depuis six mois.
And she ate a fly.
Et elle a mangé une mouche.
Seriously. six months?
Sérieux, six mois ?
Oh. my God. a treasure chest. l'm rich.
Mon Dieu, un trésor. Je suis riche.
Level three and she thinks she's rich.
Niveau trois et elle se croit riche.
What a newb.
Quelle néophyte.
Okay. we're all set.
O.K, tout est prêt.
Let her rip.
C‘est parti.
-Hi. -Hey. check it out.
- Salut. - Regarde ca.
It's just corn starch and water.
De la Mai‘zena et de l'eau.
They make up a non-Newtonian fluid which is liquid...
Ça crée un fluide non-newtonien liquide
...but solid under the percussive action of the speaker.
mais solide sous l'action du haut-parleur.
That's what makes it get all funky.
Ça le rend funky.
Yeah. okay.
Oui. O.K.
Listen. I need to talk to Sheldon.
Je dois parler a Sheldon.
No. that's what she said. Sheldon.
Non, c‘est ce qu'elle a dit, Sheldon.
Okay. I bought the game and I've been exploring the Island of Tortage.
J'ai amené le jeu et j'ai exploré l‘Ile de Tortage.
I can't figure how to pass the guard.
J'ignore comment passer le garde.
-Do you have the enchanted sword? -I have a bronze dagger.
- As-tu l'épée enchantée ? - J'ai le poignard.
You can't slay the guard with a dagger.
Tu ne peux pas l‘utiliser.
Lord. it's like the car key in your apartment door all over again.
C‘est comme pour ta clé de voiture dans ta porte.
-How do | get the sword? -Have you been to the Temple of Mitra?
- Comment avoir l'épée ? - As-tu vu le Temple ?
-The place on the hill with the priest? -No. it's--
- Sur la colline avec le prêtre ? - Non...
Oh. for God's sakes. give me.
Bon sang, donne—moi ca.
Thank you. I really appreciate this.
Merci. J'apprécie beaucoup.
You have to learn to do these things.
Tu dois apprendre ces choses—lè.
Don't patronize me. Just get the sword.
Ne sois pas condescendant.
What the frak?
C‘est quoi ce délire ?
Beats me. They were playing all last night too.
Ça me dépassé. Ils ont joué toute la soirée.
It's like some kind of weird comic-book crossover.
C‘est comme une bande dessinée bizarre.
Like if Hulk were dating Peppermint Patty.
Comme si Hulk sortait avec Peppermint Patty.
| always thought Peppermint Patty was a lesbian.
C‘était une lesbienne.
No. that's Marcie.
Non, c‘est Mamie.
Peppermint Patty's just athletic.
Peppermint Patty est juste athlétique.
There you go. one enchanted sword.
Voilà, une épée enchantée.
All right. give me. give me. I wanna kill the guard captain.
O.K, donne—moi ca. Je veux tuer le garde.
That girl needs to get a life.
Il lui faut une vie.
Sheldon.
Sheldon.
-Sheldon. -Danger. Danger.
- Sheldon. - Danger. Danger.
No danger. it's me. Penny.
Non, c‘est Penny.
Listen. I got to level 25 and reached Purple Lotus Swamp. right?
Écoute, j'ai atteint le niveau 25.
-You're in my bedroom. -Yeah.
- Tu es ici. - Oui.
-Leonard gave me an emergency key. -Peop|e can't be in my bedroom.
- Léonard m‘a donné une clé. - Ma chambre est interdite.
-Can we go talk in the living room? -|'m not wearing pajama bottoms.
- On va au salon ? - Je n'ai pas de bas de pyjama.
-Why not? -I spilled grape juice.
- Pourquoi ? - J'ai renversé du jus.
Well. wear different pajamas.
Mets-en un autre.
Can't wear different pajamas. These are my Monday pajamas.
Je ne peux pas. C‘est mon pyjama du lundi.
Penny. people cannot be in my bedroom.
Personne ne Vient dans ma chambre.
Just tell me. is it too soon to join a quest to the Black Castle?
C‘est trop tôt pour rejoindre une quête ?
You were invited on a quest to the Black Castle?
On t‘a invité a la quête du château noir ?
By some guys in Budapest. I'm just not sure it's the right move for my character.
Par des types à Budapest. Je ne sais pas si je dois le faire.
Of course it's not. You're only a level 25.
Bien sûr que non. Tu n'en es qu'au niveau 25.
These Hungarians are just using you for dragon fodder.
Ces Hongrois se servent de toi pour nourrir un dragon.
Really? Boy. you'd think you could trust a horde of Hungarian Barbarians.
Je pensais pouvoir faire confiance a une horde de barbares hongrois.
SHELDON: Please. Penny. enough. I have to sleep.
Je t'en prie Penny, ca suffit. Je dois dormir.
PENNY: Okay. well. you were great. Thanks.
Tu as été super. Merci.
Oh. Listen. don't go in Sheldon's room. He's not wearing bottoms.
Ne va pas dans sa chambre. Il est nu.
Sheldon. you wanna catch me up again?
Sheldon. tu veux m‘expliquer a nouveau ?
People. I am very busy today.
Je suis très occupé aujourd'hui.
I realize that. but it is your job as head of the department...
Je vois mais c‘est votre devoir en tant que chef
...to mediate all intra-departmental disputes.
d'arbitrer les conflits internes.
University Policy Manual. Chapter 4. subsection 2:
Chapitre 4, sous—section 2 du manuel.
“Mediation of lntra-departmental Disputes.“
“Arbitrage des conflits internes.“
Fine.
Trés bien.
Dr. Winkle. what colorful name did you call Dr. Cooper this time?
Dr Winkle, comment avez-vous surnommé Dr Cooper cette fois ?
Dr. Dumb-ass.
Dr Gros Naze.
Dr. Cooper. Dr. Winkle apologizes.
Dr Cooper, Dr Winkle s‘excuse.
-No. she doesn't. -No. I don't.
- Non.
Here's the problem. l was clearly signed up...
Voilà. J‘étais inscrit pour utiliser l'ordinateur central
...and Dr. Winkle just ripped the sign-up sheet off the wall.
et Dr Winkle a arraché la fiche d'inscription.
It wasn't an official sign-up sheet. He printed it...
Ce n‘était pas une fiche officielle.
...and he put his name down on every slot for the next six months.
Il l‘a imprimée et a mis son nom pour six mois.
If it is a crime to ensure the university's resources...
Si c‘est un crime de s‘assurer
...are not being squandered chasing subatomic wild geese...
que les ressources ne soient pas gaspillées,
...then I plead guilty.
je plaide coupable.
Oh. Penny.
Oh, Penny.
-You need to get that. Dr. Cooper? -God. no.
- C‘est urgent, Dr Cooper ? - Non.
Don't turn it off. You might miss your call from Nobel...
Ne l'éteins pas. Tu pourrais manquer
...letting you know you've been nominated...
l‘appel pour ta nomination au prix Nobel du gros naze.
Oh, yeah. well. you wouldn't even be nominated.
Ah oui ? Toi, tu ne serais même pas nominée.
l have a series of important multi-loop calculations and simulations to run.
J'ai une série importante de calculs et de simulations a faire.
She's reducing irrelevant data. making a mock--
Elle ne fait que trier des données inutiles...
Excuse me.
Excusez-moi.
Gablehauser.
Gabiehauser.
It's for you.
C‘est pour vous.
Hello?
Allô ?
Penny. this is not a good time.
Penny, ce n‘est pas le moment.
No. I told you. you're not prepared for the Sanctum of Burning Souls.
Non, tu n'es pas prête pour le repaire des âmes en feu.
You need to be in a group of at least five and one should be a level 35 healer.
Vous devez être cinq et l'un doit avoir passé le niveau 35.
No. I can't log on and help you.
Non, pas maintenant.
We'll talk when | get home.
On en reparle quand je rentre.
I'm not getting the computing time. am |?
Je n‘aurai pas l'ordinateur central, hein ?
Dumb-ass.
Gros naze.
Leonard. you have to do something about Penny.
Leonard, fais quelque chose pour Penny.
She is interfering with my sleep. She is interfering with my work.
Elle me dérange la nuit. Elle me dérange au boulot.
If I had another significant aspect of my life...
Si j‘avais autre chose dans ma vie,
...l'm sure she'd be interfering with that too.
elle me dérangerait la aussi.
Why should I do something? You introduced her to online gaming.
C‘est toi qui lui as fait découvrir les jeux.
Well. yes. but you're the one who said hello to her when she moved in.
Mais c‘est toi qui lui as dit bonjour quand elle a emménagé.
If you'd simply restrained yourself. none of this would be happening.
Si tu t‘étais retenu, rien de tout ca n‘arriverait.
-Well. just tell her to leave you alone. -I did. I told her. I texted her.
- Dis—lui de te laisser tranquille. - Je lui ai envoyé un texto.
I sent out a very emphatic Twitter. I changed my Facebook status to:
Un texto trés empathique.
I don't know what else to do.
Je ne sais pas quoi faire.
Well. what am I supposed to do?
Je suis censé faire quoi ?
If you don't figure something out. I warn you...
Si tu ne trouves pas, je te préviens
...I shall become very difficult to live with.
que je vais devenir très dur a vivre.
You mean. up until now we've been experiencing the happy fun-time Sheldon?
Tu veux dire que pour l'instant, tu étais Sheldon Ie joyeux drille ?
-Yes. -|'|| go talk to her.
- Oui. - Je vais lui parler.
No. Fritz. I need you on my flank.
Non, j'ai besoin de toi de mon côté.
No. I don't know German.
Non, je ne parle pas allemand.
-Hey. Penny? -Busy.
- Penny ? - Occupée.
Yeah. I see that. Shouldn't you be at work?
Oui, je vois. Tu n'es pas au boulot ?
I don't work on Mondays.
Pas le lundi.
lt's Thursday.
On est jeudi.
-Listen. Penny-- -Ugh. Oueen Penelope AFK. What?
- Écoute... - Reine Penelope ABS. Quoi ?
Okay. Uh....
O.K.
Here's the thing.
Voilà.
They find themselves. through no fault of their own. you know. kind of addicted.
Ils se retrouvent malgré eux, légérement accros.
Yeah. get to the point. I'm about to level up here.
Oui, accouché. Je vais franchir un niveau.
If a person doesn't have a sense of achievement in their real life...
Si une personne n‘est pas épanouie dans la vraie vie,
...it's easy to lose themselves in a world where a false sense of accomplishment--
il est facile de se perdre dans un monde où une pseudo réussite...
Yeah, jabber, jabber. jabber. Okay. boys. Oueen Penelope's back online.
Oui, et blablabla. O.K. les mecs, Reine Penelope est la.
Penny. you've got...
Penny, tu as
...Cheetos in your hair.
des chips dans les cheveux.
Oh. thanks.
Oh, merci.
LEONARD: Hey, Penny, it's ME again, Lennard.
Penny, c'est encore moi, Leonard.
PENNY: Lennard, I said, not now.
Pas main tenan !.
LEONARD: I'm just a little concerned about you and--
Je m‘inquiète pour lui et...
PENNY: I said, not now.
J'ai dit pas maintenant.
LEONARD: Okay, maybe later.
0.K, peut-être plus tard.
-Hey. guys. -Hey.
- Salut.
-Hey. what's with him? -Penny's been keeping him up at night.
- Ça va pas ? - Penny l‘empêche de dormir.
Me too.
Moi aussi.
But probably in a different way.
Mais sûrement différemment.
She's really hooked on “Age of Conan.“ She's playing non-stop.
Elle est accro à “Age of Conan.“ Elle joue non—stop.
Oh. yes. online gaming addiction.
Oui, accro aux jeux en ligne.
There's nothing worse than having that multiplayer monkey on your back.
Il n‘y a rien de pire que d‘avoir un accro du jeu sur le dos.
-She|don. wake up. -Danger. danger.
- Sheldon, réveille-toi. - Danger, danger.
Afternoon. men. Sheldon.
Salut, messieurs. Sheldon.
Oh. yeah. well. your attempt at juvenilizing me...
Oui, ta tentative de m'infantiliser
...by excluding me from the set of adult males just-- Oh. I'm too tired to do this.
en m'excluant du groupe d‘adultes mâles... Oh, je suis trop crevé pour ca.
Right. I heard you've been pulling all-nighters with Middle-Earth Barbie.
Oui. Tu as fait nuit blanche avec la Barbie dela Terre du Milieu.
She comes into my room. No one's supposed to be in my room.
Elle Vient dans ma chambre. Personne ne doit y entrer.
I would postulate she's escaping into the online world...
Elle se réfugie dans le monde Virtuel pour
...to compensate for her sexual frustration.
compenser sa frustration sexuelle.
I do that too.
Je fais ca aussi.
But probably in a different way.
Mais sûrement différemment.
That's not what she's doing. Leslie.
Ce n‘est pas ce qu'elle fait.
She's trying to shore up her self-esteem. It has nothing to do with sex.
Elle reprend confiance en elle. Le sexe n‘a rien a voir.
Everything has to do with sex.
Le sexe est partout.
Mm. Testify.
Prouve-le.
I'm not touching that.
Je ne touche pas ca.
-Leslie. you are way off base here. -Now. hang on. Leonard.
- Tu es a côté dela plaqué. - Attends.
While I have no respect for Leslie as a scientist...
Je n'ai aucun respect pour Leslie Ia scientifique et la femme
...we have to concede her undeniable expertise...
mais il faut reconnaître son expertise
...in the interrelated fields of promiscuity and general sluttiness.
dans les domaines dela promiscuité et l'allumage en général.
Thank you.
Merci.
My point is that Tinkerbell just needs to get her some.
Bref, la Fée Clochette en a besoin.
Some what? Oh. yes. some sexual intercourse.
De quoi ? Ah, oui, d'un rapport sexuel.
I'll take the bullet.
Je m‘y collé.
-Excuse me. this whole idea's insane. -Enough debate. I'm going to take action.
- Cette idée est absurde. - Assez discuté. Je vais agir.
Excuse me.
Excuse-moi.
Are you currently involved in a sexual relationship?
Es-tu actuellement impliqué dans une relation sexuelle ?
-No. -Would you like to be?
- Non. - Aimerais-tu l'être ?
Sure. why not?
Oui, pourquoi pas ?
-She|don-- -Yip. yip. yip.
Sheldon. ..
Can I have your phone number?
Tu peux me donner ton numéro ?
Yeah.
Oui.
There. problem solved.
Voilà, probléme réglé.
Dumb-ass.
Gros naze.
Okay. I'm at the gate to the Treasury of the Ancients. I'm going in.
Je suis devant la porte du Trésor des anciens.
Stay close to the wall.
- Longe le mur. Evite les momies. - O.K.
I must say. you're playing very well for a woman of 23?
Je dois dire, tu joues bien pour une femme de 23 ans.
-Twenty-two. -Right. 22.
- 22. - Oui, 22.
Here come the mummies. Which spell do I use?
Quel sort j‘utilise ? Le coup haineux ou la position frénétique?
What happened to your group?
- Et ton groupe ? - Je les ai largués. Des poules mouillées.
Frenzy stance.
La frénésie.
Frenzy. frenzy. frenzy.
Frénésie, frénésie, frénésie.
So listen. would you describe your ideal vacation...
Tes vacances idéales seraient plutôt
...as a wild adventure to unknown lands or staying at home with a good book?
une folie aventure dans un pays inconnu ou rester chez toi avec un bon livre ?
-Wait. what? -These are market-research questions.
- Quoi ? - C‘est une étude de marché.
l'm filling out the online registration for your game.
Je remplis le formulaire en ligne pour ton jeu.
Oh. okay. wild adventure.
Une folie aventure.
Oh. frenzy stance isn't working.
Le sort ne marche pas.
-Die. you undead mummy. die! -Drink a healing potion.
- Meurs, momie ! - Bois une potion curative.
-Thank you. -You're welcome.
- Merci. - De rien.
Anyhow. on a scale of one to five...
Sur une échelle de un a cinq,
...with one being. “always initiated by him“...
un étant "toujours initié par lui“ et cinq "toujours initié par toi“
...how do you prefer your sexual encounters to begin?
comment préfères-tu que tes rapports sexuels commencent ?
That's on the registration?
C‘est sur le formulaire ?
Oh. yes. it's quite extensive.
Oui, il est assez complet.
If we complete it. you get a free expansion pack.
Si on le remplit, tu reçois un cadeau.
Seventy-five additional quests.
75 quêtes supplémentaires.
Oh. awesome. Okay. I totally like to initiate. I'm a big old five.
Génial. J‘adore initier les rapports. 5, sans hésiter.
Good to know.
Bon a savoir.
Big old five.
Réponse 5, sans hésiter.
-He||o. -Hi.
- Salut.
Leonard. this is Tom.
Leonard, voici Tom.
Hi. Tom. Sheldon.
Salut Tom, Sheldon.
Didn't I explain to you about your little mistake in the cafeteria?
Je ne t'ai pas expliqué ta petite erreur a la cafétéria ?
Yes. you were very clear. as was everyone else at the table.
Si, tu as été très clair, comme les autres.
Tom. however. has been chosen by science as a suitable mate for Penny.
Tom a été choisi parla science comme copain approprié pour Penny.
Chosen by science.
Choisi parla science.
Well. what passes for science on dating sites.
Enfin, la science des sites de rencontres.
They may claim to use heuristic algorithms. but it may well be hokum.
Ils prétendent utiliser des algorithmes heuristiques.
You got Penny to sign up for online dating?
Tu as convaincu Penny de s'inscrire ?
No. no. of course not. No. see. I used trickery and deceit.
Non, bien sûr que non. J'ai utilisé la tromperie et la dissimulation.
This is bad.
C‘est pas bon.
Tom is a paramedic with the fire department.
Tom est secouriste.
He's going to med school.
Il fait médecine.
Uh. he likes the outdoors and. uh. strong women who initiate sex.
Il aime le grand air et les femmes qui initient le sexe.
Really. really bad.
Pas bon du tout.
I'm surprised you struck out with Penny. Apparently. she's a big old five.
Surprenant que ça ait pas marché avec Penny. Elle a mis réponse 5.
-She|don. what do you want? -Oh. good. you got my note.
- Que veux-tu ? - Tu as eu mon message.
Penny. I'd like you to meet Tom. Uh. Penny. this is Tom.
Penny, je te présente Tom. Penny, voici Tom.
-Tom. may I present Penny. -Hi. Penny.
- Tom, je te présente Penny. - Salut.
Hi. as long as I'm here...
Je fais une quête avec des néophytes, ils ne pigent rien.
Got one assassin. three spell casters. no tank.
Un assassin, trois jeteurs de sorts.
-Can we talk later? -No. I need you now.
- Plus tard. - Non, maintenant.
Wouldn't you prefer to socialize with Tom...
Ne veux-tu pas parler avec Tom.
...who is a sexually passive outdoorsman?
un homme de plein air sexuellement passif ?
-Whatever. l'll figure it out myself. -Bye. Penny.
- Tant pis, je me débrouillerais. - Au revoir, Penny.
I'm sorry. dude. she didn't look anything like her picture.
Désolé, mec. elle n‘était pas comme sur la photo.
They never do.
Ce n‘est jamais le cas.
H OWARD: Hello, lair Penny.
Bonjour, julie Penny.
PENNY: Who are you? HOWARD: It is I, Sir Howard of Wolowitz.
- Qui es-tu ? - C'est moi, Sir Howard de Wolowitz.
Can I interest you in an afternoon of spirited questing...
Que dis-tu d'une après-midi de quête fougueuse
...Iollowed by a Ilagon of ale at yon virtual tavern?
suivie d ’un pichet de bière a‘ la taverne ?
PENNY: Yeah, sure, why not?
Oui, pourquoi pas ?
Oh. my God. I need help.
Mon Dieu, j'ai besoin d‘aide.
[ENGLISH SDH]
[FRENCH]